(Penny:)Come on. It's still early.
Let's do something.
(Sheldon:)Well, I have been toying around
with an idea for 4D chess.
(Penny:)-How about we just talk?
-All right.
(Sheldon:)-In 4D chess--
-No.
(Penny:)Come on, let's talk about our lives.
(Penny:)Tell me something
about you I don't know.
(Sheldon:)I own nine pairs of pants.
Okay, that's a good start,
(Penny:)but I was thinking maybe something
a little more personal.
(Raj:)-I see.
-Hm.
(Sheldon:)I own nine pairs of underpants.
(Penny:)How about I go first?
(Sheldon:)But I don't want to know
how many underpants you own.
(Sheldon:)Although, based on the floor of your
bedroom, I'd say it's a thousand.
(Penny:)Okay, look, here's something
people do not know about me.
(Penny:)When I first moved out to LA,
(Penny:)I did a topless scene
in a low-budget horror movie